http://www.odeon.co.uk/privacy-and-legal/

Sign in to MyODEONPassword
Username or Password incorrect.
Not signed up?Sign up nowForgotten your password?
Forgotten your password?Enter the email address you registered with and we will email you a link to reset your password
Dorchester
Dudley (Merry Hill)
ODEON Luxe
This is cinema like you've never experienced before.
iSense
Enjoy epic cinema with iSense
Premier Seating
The best seats in the house.
Food & Drink
Sweets, Ice cream, soft drinks, fresh popcorn & hot food.
3D
3D images that pop out of the screen.
IMAX
Immerse yourself in the action with ODEON IMAX.
The Gallery
VIP bar area, unlimited popcorn, nachos & soft drink.
Our cinemas are available for Corporate Events, Conferences and Private Screenings. "Visit our website."
TENET
Cats & Dogs: Paws Unite!
Black Panther
Bohemian Rhapsody (2020)
Bolshoi Ballet: Romeo And Juliet (2020)
Bolshoi: The Lady Of The Camellias (2020)
Booksmart
Cabin In The Woods
Cats & Dogs: Paws Unite!
Coco (2020)
Coco.
Deadpool (2020)
Dirty Dancing (30th Anniversary)
Emma.
Kajillionaire
La Haine SFL - Subtitled Foreign Language (Bring Back)
La La Land
Love Actually (Bring Back)
The New Mutants
The Royal Ballet: Giselle (2020)
Original British Cinema
All the best live & recorded performances from around the world. You'll feel like you're there.
View ODEON Event Cinema performances
Top 5 Films Now Booking
TENET
Cats & Dogs: Paws Unite!
ODEON Gift Card
Sign up to MyODEON for a chance to win a free year of Limitless
Find out more
Terms & Conditions
Sign up
ODEON Gift Cards
Why not treat family and friends to a gift as magical as cinema itself with our ODEON Gift Cards.
you want, as often as you like*
Imagine being able to see all the films you want, week in, week out.
Mid-week romcom? Saturday night blockbuster?
With huge potential savings and access to exclusive member treats, joining Limitless means you can watch all the films you want as often as you like for one monthly fee.
Join now from just £15.99 a month*.
*Terms and conditions apply. Extra charge for some screenings and facilities.
£15.99/month membership excludes Central London cinemas.
Price including Central London cinemas is £17.99/month.
Minimum age is 16, minimum membership period is 12 months, and monthly payment is by Direct Debit.
Find out more
ODEON Luxe
Select your ODEON Luxe Experience
Select a cinema
Aylesbury - ODEON Luxe
Birmingham Broadway Plaza - ODEON Luxe
Bromborough - ODEON Luxe
Darlington - ODEON Luxe
Go
Your new luxury cinemas, where every seat reclines.
Relax, recline and experience your new ODEON Luxe cinema. With handmade luxury reclining seats in
every screen, you'll have more space and comfort to truly immerse yourself in the moment
and escape into film. Sample the new selection of fine wines and beers from Oscar's Bar,
which sit perfectly alongside our irresistible food menu.
This is just you and the film – cinema has never felt better.
Find out more
Privacy & Legal (UK)
1. PRIVACY POLICY (Version 4.3 dated September 2020)
The Privacy Policy helps you understand how ODEON may collect and use your personal information, and the choices you can make about how your personal information is used.
2. COOKIE POLICY (Version 2.0 dated July 2020)
The Cookie Policy helps you understand how cookies and similar technologies are used on the ODEON website, and the choices you can make about this.
3. PRIVACY SUMMARY (Version 1.0 dated June 2020)
The Privacy Summary sets out a summary of how ODEON may collect and use your personal information.
4. LIMITLESS TERMS AND CONDITIONS (Version 4.0 dated July 2020)
The  Limitless Terms and Conditions set out the legally binding terms which apply to everyone who joins Limitless.
5. ONLINE PURCHASE TERMS AND CONDITIONS (Version 4.1 dated August 2020)
The Online Purchase Terms and Conditions set out the legally binding terms which apply to the purchase of tickets, food and drink online or on our app. 6. WEBSITE TERMS OF USE (Version 3.0 dated June 2020)
The Website Terms of Use set out the legally binding terms which apply to everyone who accesses or uses our website or our app
7. GENERAL ADMISSION TERMS (Version 1.0 dated May 2009)
The General Admission Terms set out the legally binding terms generally applicable to the issue of a ticket and to your subsequent access to an ODEON Cinema. 8. ODEON UK GIFT CARD TERMS OF USE (Version 3.7 dated December 2019)
The ODEON Gift Card Terms of Use set out the legally binding terms and conditions of use for an ODEON gift card.
9. ODEON SOCIAL MEDIA PRIZE DRAW TERMS AND CONDITIONS (Version 2.0 dated June 2020)
These terms set out the legally binding terms and conditions which apply to the competitions and prize draws we run on our social media channels unless otherwise stated.
10. LIMITLESS GIFT MEMBERSHIP CARD & VOUCHER CODE TERMS OF USE (Version 1.1 dated May 2019).
The Limitless Gift Membership Card & Voucher Code Terms of Use set out the legally binding terms which apply to everyone who uses a Limitless gift membership card or voucher code.
11. WI-FI TERMS OF USE (Version 3.0 dated June 2020)
The Wi-Fi Terms of Use set out the legally binding terms and conditions which apply to the use of ODEON Wi-Fi in cinemas.
12. MYODEON UK & REPUBLIC OF IRELAND PRIZE DRAW TERMS (Version 1.1 dated May 2019)
The MyODEON Prize Draw Terms and Conditions set out the legally binding terms and conditions which apply to the MyODEON prize draw.
13.  LIMITLESS RESTAURANT OFFER TERMS AND CONDITIONS (Version 1.0 dated February 2019)
The Limitless Restaurant Offer Terms and Conditions set out the legally binding terms and conditions which apply to the Limitless Restaurant Offer.
14. TELL ODEON UK & REPUBLIC OF IRELAND PRIZE DRAW TERMS AND CONDITIONS (Version 1.1 dated May 2019)
The Tell ODEON Prize Draw Terms and Conditions set out the legally binding terms and conditions which apply to our Tell ODEON prize draw.
15. MEERKAT MOVIES AT ODEON TERMS AND CONDITIONS (Version 3.1 dated June 2020)
The Meerkat Movies at ODEON Terms and Conditions supplement the Meerkat Movies 241 offer, by setting out how you can use your Meerkat Movies 241 code at an ODEON cinema.
COMPANY INFORMATION
ODEON CINEMAS LIMITED
Registered Address: c/o Shoosmiths LLP, 100 Avebury Boulevard, Milton Keynes MK9 1FH
Registered in England under company number 1854132. Registered for VAT under VAT number 241717672.
For more information about how to contact us, please visit the 'Contact Us' page of this website.
EXPLORE OUR SITE
Find a cinema
London Cinemas
What's on Now
Cinema Tickets
ODEON films blog
THE ODEON EXPERIENCE
ODEON Kids
ODEON Magazine
Mobile Site:
ODEON App:
© ODEON Cinemas Holdings Limited 2006 to 2020 - All rights reserved.
Privacy and Legal
|
Sitemap
Sorry this performance is sold out, please check for other available performances
Sorry, this performance is not available.
Sorry, this performance is only available at the box office.
G
Gallery showing
(over 18s only)
Kids Screen
(With kids soft seating area)
Starts:
Screen:
Book now
Booking is temporarily unavailable. Please try again later.
Free passes restricted - Find out more
This is an Audio Described Performance: This performance is Audio Described for the visually impaired via headphones available from the Box Office.
This is a Limitless Screening Performance: This performance is exclusive to ODEON Limitless members. If you’re not a member yet, join now.
This is a Subtitled Performance: Displays subtitles on screen to benefit guests who may be hard of hearing.
Important - this performance is in the early hours of the date shown. E.g Tues 00:15 would be first showing, early hours of Tuesday morning/late night Monday. Find out more
Note - Please note this is an early morning AM performance for the date listed, not an afternoon/evening PM performance. Find out more
